

Kateřina Hrubá

DESIGNER

ABOUT

I am a graphic and media design student. I consider myself to be open-minded, creative, and with a sense of punctuality. I am passionate about all forms of art but mostly about design and photography. I think of myself as a positive and communicative person with a sense of empathy. I have no problem working in a team and I am always excited to learn new things. I am a hard worker and I don't like to do things at the last minute.

I enjoy traveling and getting to know other cultures and people. During my high school studies, I traveled abroad twice for half a year. First I spent 6 months in the US where I attended high school in Colorado. Two years later I visited Australia. Both of these experiences thought me independence, problem-solving ability, and the ability to work in a multicultural setting. One of my other passions in life is swimming so don't be surprised when you run into me with wet hair.

SKILLS

I can work with most of the programs in Adobe creative cloud (Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, Xd, Lighroom, Premier).

I try to look outside the box with every one of my projects and I think the key to a success in the field of graphic design is communication between the designer and the client.

Also, I am capable of producing product pictures or lifestyle pictures for proffesional or personal use.

LANGUAGES

Czech / native
English / C1, proficient
Spanish / B1, intermediate
French / A1, beginner

EXPERIENCE

June 2020 - Present

Wedding Factory

Part-time wedding arranger and designer

Designing and arranging wedding venues.
Responsible for decorations and design. Part-time coordinating weddings. Coordinating guests and everyone involved in the wedding.

January 2020 - June 2020

Magazine Šestka

Internship-External designer

External designer for a magazine at Prague 6. Work involved designing posters and infographics for Prague 6.

January 2019 - May 2019

Swim&Relax shop

Part-time saleswoman

A part-time job at a shop with swimming equipment. Selling swimming equipment at Podolí swimming pool. Also included receiving goods, processing e-shop orders, and inventory counting.

Summer 2017 - 2019

Sara MB

Lifeguard

Working at an outdoor swimming pool as a summer job. Included having a lifeguard course.

EDUCATION

2018 - Currently studying (3rd year)

■ VŠKK,Prague

Graphic and media design specialization.

A three-year study programme with bachelor degree.

2010 - 2018

GMVV, Prague

Eight-year high school specialized in languages and international relations.